https://pl.com.au/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentPrivacy Policy Privacy Policy2019-08-06T23:31:37+10:00Parke Lawyers Pty Ltd is committed to providing quality legal services and this policy outlines our ongoing obligations in respect of how we manage personal information.Parke Lawyers complies with the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Spam Act 2003 (Cth). The APPs govern the way in which we collect, use, disclose, store, secure and dispose of your personal information. A copy of the APPs may be obtained from the website of the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner.Policy principlesWhat personal information do we collect?Personal information is information or an opinion that identifies an individual. Examples of personal information we collect include: names, addresses, email addresses, phone numbers, age, gender, human resources information and individual preferences.This personal information is obtained in many ways including interviews, correspondence, by phone and facsimile, by email, via our website www.pl.com.au, from your website, from media and publications, from other publicly available sources, from cookies and from third parties. We do not guarantee website links or policy of third party websites. Where reasonable and practicable to do so, we will collect your personal information directly from you. In some circumstances we may be provided with information by third parties.For what is the information used?We collect your personal information for the primary purposes of providing our services to you, providing information to our clients and marketing. We may also use your personal information for secondary purposes closely related to the primary purposes, in circumstances where you would reasonably expect such use or disclosure.When we collect personal information we will, where appropriate and where possible, explain to you why we are collecting the information and how we plan to use it.Anti-spamIn compliance with the Spam Act 2003, the supply by you of an email address will be taken as consent to receive electronic messages from us. Any mailing/marketing communication you receive electronically from us will identify it is from Parke Lawyers and will provide a facility for you to unsubscribe from future electronic messages.Disclosure of personal informationYour personal information may be disclosed in a number of circumstances including the following:With your consent;To a person authorised to act on your behalf; andWhere required or authorised by law.Security of personal informationPhysical, electronic and procedural safeguards are used to ensure information security, thereby protecting your personal information from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.When your personal information is no longer needed for the purpose for which it was obtained, we will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify your personal information. Most personal information is or will be stored and kept by us for a minimum of seven years.Access to your personal informationWe will, in most circumstances, make available to you upon written request any personal information about you that has been collected. We will not charge any fee for your access request, but may charge an administrative fee for providing a copy of your personal information. In order to protect your personal information we may require identification from you before releasing the requested information.Maintaining the quality of your personal informationIt is an important to us that your personal information is up-to-date. We will take reasonable steps to make sure your personal information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If you find the information we have is not up-to-date or is inaccurate, you should advise us as soon as practicable so we can update our records thereby ensuring continuing provision of quality services to you.Policy updatesThis policy may change from time-to-time and is available on our website.Privacy policy complaints and enquiriesIf you have any queries or complaints about our privacy policy, please contact us at:GPO Box 66 MELBOURNE  VIC  3001Email: law@pl.com.au Phone: 134 134About UsOur HistoryOur ClientsWhy Choose Parke LawyersAwardsQuality SystemInformation SecurityHealth & SafetyCorporate Social ResponsibilityFAQsCostsReferralsISO AccreditationsResources
Go to Top
